{
    "id": "fbbfdee56eac4581bc0777bfc23cf0f7",
    "title": "Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The country is —————– by factions.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "teared",
                "tore",
                "torn"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Once Sydney Smith was asked his name by a servant and found to his dismay that he had —————— his own name.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "forget",
                "forgot",
                "forgotten"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You couldn’t have —————- a better day for a drive.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "chose",
                "chosen",
                "choosed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The old beggar was —————— by a mad dog.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "byte",
                "bitten"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He —————– the book on the table.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lay",
                "laid",
                "lain"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Walking through the jungle he —————- on a snake.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "treaded",
                "trode",
                "troded"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He —————— a hasty retreat on the arrival of a policeman.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "beat",
                "beated",
                "beaten"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You must reap what you have —————–",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sow",
                "sown",
                "sowed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "His voice —————- as he spoke.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shook",
                "shaken",
                "shaked"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "His path was not —————– with flowers but he persevered.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "strawn",
                "strewn",
                "strewed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The explorers were ————— to death.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "froze",
                "frozen",
                "freezed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "His voice —————— to a whisper.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sink",
                "sank",
                "sunk"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}